// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What's 1+0?",
    answer: "1",
    options: [
      "1",
      "2",
      "3",
      "4"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What's 1+1?",
    answer: "2",
    options: [
      "1",
      "2",
      "3",
      "4"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What's 1+2?",
    answer: "3",
    options: [
      "1",
      "2",
      "3",
      "4"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What's 1+3?",
    answer: "4",
    options: [
      "1",
      "2",
      "3",
      "4"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What's 1+4?",
    answer: "5",
    options: [
      "5",
      "2",
      "3",
      "4"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What's 1+5?",
    answer: "6",
    options: [
      "5",
      "6",
      "3",
      "4"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "What's 1+6?",
    answer: "7",
    options: [
      "5",
      "2",
      "7",
      "4"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "What's 1+7?",
    answer: "8",
    options: [
      "5",
      "2",
      "3",
      "8"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "What's 1+8?",
    answer: "9",
    options: [
      "5",
      "2",
      "9",
      "4"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "What's 1+9?",
    answer: "10",
    options: [
      "5",
      "10",
      "3",
      "4"
    ]
  }
]